<resources>
    <string name="app_name">X Ed</string>

    <string name="createAccount">
        How to open a bank Account:\n\n
Select your type of account. There are usually 2 types of accounts:\n
A. A Savings Account\n
B. A current Account\n\n
A savings Account basically helps you gain intrest on the money you store in the bank,
        But you would require a minimum amount in the abnk at all times.
A current account is based for daily uses and has no lower limit and neither does it provide an Intrest.\n\n\n

Wanna know more?\n\n

Scroll Down...\n\n\n

Next you have to provide your personal details along with relevant proof.\n
The proofs required include an ID proof and an Address proof.\n\n
Of recently banks require your aadhar number also to make the process smoother.\n
You will also need to supply them with a photograph and fill up a form for the application.\n\n
If you are a minor then you would need your parents to sign off and be the custodians till you become 18 years.\n\n
You then put in your initial balance into the account by either giving a draft or cash.\n
You then wait for a couple of business days till you recieve your cheque book and accompanying kit.\n\n\n

Thats all for bank account creation.\n
    </string>

    <string name="deposit">
Methods of Depositing:\n\n
 a. Cash: You can give cash to the teller and fill up a deposit
    form available at the counter to deposit money through cash.\n
 b. Demand Draft or Cashiers Cheque: You can Deposit cash that
    is verified by a teller by providing a DD.\n
 c. Online transfer: One can transfer using online portal from
    another account provided you have the account number, NEFT
    or IFSC codes.\n
 d. Cheques: You can deposit a cheque with you account number
    and contact details written at the back and get the money
    deposited in 3-4 business days.\n
    </string>

    <string name="withdraw">
Withdrawing cash:\n\n
 a. Cash: Again you can use the ATM with your debit card to get
    the cash. Or fill up a form at your bank branch and request
    the teller to provide you with the cash.\n
 b. Demand Draft: Provide the details of whom the money is
    supposed to be given to and the reason the teller then
    generates an official note that can then be deposited by the
    other party directly into his account.\n
 c. Cheque: Draw up a cheque in favour of your reciepient or a
    self addressed cheque and give it to the other person.\n
    </string>

    <string name="invOpportunities">
Investment Opportunities:\n\n\n
A customer of the bank can invest in any of the following options:\n\n
 a. Fixed Deposits: These are deposits into a bank that can be
    frozen in for a period of time and they accumulate interest
    over this period.\n
 b. Bonds: These are government sponsored guarantees that so much
    amount will be payed with a particular amount of intrest.\n
 c. Stock Options: Buying a share in a particular company and
    investing based on the profits or losses of that company and
    its performance in the market.\n
    </string>

    <string name="doDont">
Do\'s of banking:\n\n
 a. Read your statements\n
 b. Keep record of all transactions\n
 c. Make sure you have enough money before a purchase\n
 d. Keep all bank related documents safe and secure.\n
 e. Be nice to customer service.\n
 f. Protect your personal information\n\n\n
Dont\'s of banking:\n\n
 a. Ask for statements to be stopped.\n
 b. Bluff and threatent customer service\n
 c. Depend on ATM's for balance\n
 d. Throw away reciepts\n
 e. Keeps using debit card even after wrong PIN.\n
 f. Gives Away account details to anyone.\n
    </string>
</resources>
